# KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



## PERSONAL SKILLS

- Emotional Awareness
- Problem Solving
- Individual Collaboration
- Relationship Development
- Research & Market Expansion

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails (Ruby)
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite / PostgreSQL
- GitHub

## LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

## INTERESTS

- Weight Training
- American Football
- Specialty Coffee
- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)

# CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

## - My Portfolio:

https://keiichi031605.github.io/keiichi-portfolio/

Linkedin: keiichi katsuno
GitHub: keiichi031605

## **PROFILE**

Ruby on Rails Developer. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about business improvement that has a real influence on people's life.

For the past 6 years, I've experienced Marketing and Relationship Development in Japan, and Production Management in The UK and Colombia. I've been focusing on solving the problems and meeting the needs of clients as well as team members. Therefore, I've developed the ability to **collaborate individually** to work in a team and **build firm relationships** with diverse people.

I place a high value on **respect to people** and **learning independently** in my life.

# EXPERIENCE

#### **QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST**

InverCafé Ltda., Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (Internship)

- Responsibility: Quality Control of Harvested Green Coffee Products
- Developed: "Deep Industrial Knowledge" and "Marketing Research"

## PRODUCTION MANAGER

The Roasting Shed Co., London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019 (Full-time)

- Responsibility: Production Management of High-Quality Coffee Products
- Developed: "Production Analysis & Development and "Marketing Research"

#### **RELATIONSHIP MANAGER**

Yuasa Trading Co., Osaka & Fukuoka, Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017 (Full-time)

- **Responsibility:** Partnership Development and Account & Order Management. Achieved doubling my area sales targets within a 12-month period while ensuring firm relationships with pertners.
- Developed: "Sales & Marketing", "Project Management" and "Negotiation"

## **EDUCATION**

## **BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, SPORTS MANAGEMENT**

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

Outside of study, engaged in American Football club, learning Organisational Theory & Team Management and Logical & Critical Thinking for organisational success.

## **PROJECT**

#### "WHATSPOT" (SPOT SHARING SERVICE)

- The mobile apprication that you can share any places or recommendations with your friends so that you get more trustable information for your weekend! **URL:** https://www.whatsthespot.com